(Sheldon:)He's trying to video chat.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps I shouldn't have
taken this into the real world.
Oh, really?
PENNY: "'Time travel?
I don't understand,'
"said Amelia.
Cooper stared at her.
'Which word don't you
understand, time or travel?'"
(Bernadette:)Wow, even in your fantasies
Sheldon's kind of exhausting.
(Amy:)He's like that
in the beginning,
(Amy:)so she can change him.
(Amy:)It's called good writing.
(Amy:)And wishful thinking.
"It stung Amelia
"when he spoke to her this way.
"In her little
one-room schoolhouse,
"she was always
the smartest student,
"regularly besting the boys
in her class,
"but this was no boy
in front of her--
"this was a man.
(Bernadette:)Here we go.
"Cooper told Amelia
"about all the strange
and incredible things
"the future would hold,
like computers
"and living past 30.
"He asked her
if she had any questions.
"All she longed to ask was
"if his heart was beating
as fast as hers,